fuckpartner.com 2011-11-01

# Adult Dating & Adult Personals - Swingers, Women, Men, Couples - FuckPartner.com

We are committed to protecting our users' privacy!

We at FuckPartner™, an Internet property of FP Internet Limited (“FuckPartner™,” “we” or “us”) offer this Privacy Policy ("Policy") to inform users (“Users”) of www.fuckpartner.com (the "Website") how we define, collect, use and disclose the personal information that they provide to us. You agree to this Policy, in its entirety, when you: (a) access or use the Website; (b) provide personal information to us via the Website, or by other means; (c) register on the Website to receive our membership-based, adult-themed social networking services (“Service”); (d) register for one of the contests and/or promotions conducted through the Website; and/or (e) obtain, or attempt to obtain, any products and/or services featured on the Website.

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to alter this Policy at any time; provided, however, that any amendment or modification to the arbitration provisions, prohibition on class actions provisions or any other provisions applicable to dispute resolution (collectively, “Dispute Resolution Provisions”) shall not apply to any disputes arising prior to the applicable amendment or modification. Alterations shall become effective immediately once posted on the Website (other than with respect to disputes arising prior to the amendment or modification of the Dispute Resolution Provisions, which shall be governed by the Dispute Resolution Provisions then in effect at the time of the subject dispute). We will notify you of a substantive change to this Policy by posting a notice of such substantial change on the home page of the Website and we may also email you to notify you of such changes. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of changes and/or modifications will constitute your acceptance of the revised Policy.

Please read this Policy carefully and save it. If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy, you should leave the Website and discontinue use of the Service immediately. In addition, if you are an individual who wishes to become a “Registered User” or “Member” (as those terms are defined in the FuckPartner™ Website Terms and Conditions (“Terms and Conditions”)), you must read this Policy and indicate your acceptance of its terms by following the instructions on the registration page and check the box labeled "I have read and agree to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions. I confirm I have reached the age of majority in my jurisdiction."

For the purposes of this Policy, "personal information" shall mean any information that can identify an individual directly or through other reasonable means.

**If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third party for marketing purposes, please e-mail us at:[help@fuckpartner.com](mailto:help@fuckpartner.com). Please be advised that where California residents opt-out from permitting their personal information to be shared, such individuals may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with the law.**

When you register on our Website, you hereby agree and acknowledge that your personal information will be placed into the FuckPartner™ database and that such personal information shall be shared with third parties for marketing purposes.

## 1) Information We Gather Automatically.

Each time a visitor visits the Website, our servers collect certain non-personal technical information including, but not necessarily limited to, the visitor's IP Address, referral data and browser/platform type. This information is recorded by the standard operation of FuckPartner's™ Internet servers. We also count, track and aggregate a visitor's activity and input the data into our analysis of general traffic flows at the Website (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the Website, etc.). The information collected in connection with this process cannot identify any individuals. However, we may use your IP addresses in cooperation with your Internet provider to identify you if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with this Policy, our Terms and Conditions or to protect our Service, the Website, Registered Users, Members or others.

We may merge information about visitors and visits into group data, which may then at our discretion be shared on an aggregated basis with third parties including, without limitation, advertisers and marketing companies.

**What are IP Addresses?** An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider whenever you're surfing the Internet. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information, which means that your session will be logged anonymously.

**What are Cookies?** We use cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements, and to customize advertising and web page content for individual users. A cookie is an alphanumeric identifier which we transfer to your hard drive through your web browser when you visit our Website. It enables our own system to recognise you when you visit our Website again and improve the delivery of our Service to you. Cookies may also be used to compile aggregate information about areas of our Website that are visited most frequently.

This traffic information can be used to enhance the content of our Website and make your use of it easier. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on the Website. Note that you must enable cookies from FuckPartner.com in order to use most functions on the Website. Nevertheless, if you wish to reject our cookies, you can configure your browser to do so (instructions for disabling cookies can be found in our FAQs here). Please note that FuckPartner™ allows third parties who are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer in a process that FuckPartner™ does not control. Advertisers' uses of cookies are subject to their own privacy policies, not this Policy. Therefore, we suggest that you examine the privacy policies of such advertisers to learn how they may collect, use, share and disclose your personal information. To find out more about cookies, please visit www.cookiecentral.com.

## 2) Information Required for Registration.

The type of personal information that we may request depends on and is related to the reason (or purpose) such personal information was provided to us. During the process to become a Registered User and/or Member (collectively, “User”) of the Website, we ask for general identifying information to provide you with customized Service. We gather personal contact information such as screen name, email address and some demographic information such as age, gender and general geographic location. Any other information you choose to enter, such as your personal interests and preferences and general indications of the type of partner you are looking for using the Service, is completely optional.

We encourage Users to fill out their profiles as completely as possible, with the understanding that, once entered, contact information is treated anonymously and is not available to other FuckPartner™ Users. Profile information may include, without limitation, ethnic background, appearance and features, religion, income range, occupation, sexual preference/lifestyle information. **Any communications from other Users are done via our internal systems, which are used to match the message to you and generate an e-mail notification without disclosing any of your information to other Users aside from your chosen screen name.**

The choice to provide us with your personal information is always yours. However, your decision to withhold particular information may result in limiting our ability to respond to your inquiries or provide you with the Service that you requested.

Note that, during the Membership process, third party billing agents will collect personally identifiable information required to process payments for the Service and/or products and/or services sold on the Website. This information may include, but is not limited to: email address, first name, last name, date of birth, credit card number and/or checking account information for payment, a mailing address, zip code and telephone number. FuckPartner™ retains this information to correctly identify you in dealings with third party billing agents. Additional information gathered by third party billing agents is not controlled by FuckPartner™ or this Policy.

To the extent that FuckPartner™ collects your credit card-specific information, if ever, we will use this information to process and complete any transaction that you request. By submitting your credit card information to us, you authorize FuckPartner™ to periodically verify that your credit card account continues to be a valid and active one by charging, and thereafter immediately crediting, a small sum to the card. Such verification may be conducted through a third-party and, in that case, FuckPartner™ would share your specific credit card information with this third-party for verification purposes. Apart from said uses, we will not share your credit card information with any third parties without your prior informed consent. Notwithstanding the foregoing, FuckPartner™ reserves the right to share with third parties the fact that we have credit card information on file for specific Users, but we will not share your specific credit card information with third-parties without your prior informed consent. 

## 3) Voluntary Inclusion of Personal Information.

Personally identifiable information that you enter into your profile, that you include in communications with other Users, that you disclose in any media (text, chat streams, graphical, audio, visual or audio-visual) or that you post or display on the Website is accessible by other Users of the Website. FuckPartner™ is not responsible for any privacy issues arising from your own voluntary posting or transmission of personal information via the Service. You acknowledge and agree that you (not FuckPartner™ or its affiliates, advertisers, employees and/or content providers) shall be solely responsible and liable for all damages, liability or other consequences, foreseen or unforeseen, of all information which you submit, publish, display, disseminate or otherwise communicate through the Website even if a claim for damages or liability should arise after termination of Service. 

## 4) Communication.

The Website directly communicates with Users, and facilitates communication between Users via, through email, instant messaging and, in some cases, downloaded executables. This enables Users to receive information when they are not on the Website, so they remain current on internal communication and updates from other Users or from us directly. The Website may also use personally identifiable information within your profile to send information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as special banners and promotions. Should you not wish FuckPartner™ to send you information on other services or products, please contact us using the information provided in Section 17 below.

Users of the Website can directly communicate with you through messaging services that are part of the Service (mail, chat or via comments). We may use personally identifiable information within your profile to send notifications of these communications to you, but your personally identifiable information is not disclosed to other Users by us. 

## 5) Referrals.

If you choose to use our external referral service to tell a friend about the Website, we will ask you for your friend's contact information. We will automatically send your friend an e-mail inviting them to visit the Website. We maintain this information for the sole purpose of sending this email and tracking the success of the referral. 

## 6) Your Use of Other Users' Information.

You may not use other Users' information for commercial purposes, to send SPAM or SPIM, to harass, to make unlawful threats or for any other illegal purpose. FuckPartner™ reserves the right to terminate the Service for anyone who misuses other Users' information.

If you receive communications that you believe have violated this Policy, please contact us using the information provided in Section 17 below, being sure to include the content of the communication in question and the User who sent the communication to you. 

## 7) Accuracy of Personal Information, Information Review and Removal.

We shall make every reasonable effort to ensure your personal information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. You are responsible for advising FuckPartner™ of any inaccuracies or changes to your personal information.

Users may modify or remove any of their information associated with their profile at any time by logging into their account and accessing the “Edit Profile” feature.

Users may, at any time, delete their profiles or remove any images or audio-visual material that they have posted to the Website. 

## 8) Promotions.

From time to time, FuckPartner™ may sponsor sweepstakes, contests or other events of interest to our Users (collectively, “Promotions”). FuckPartner™ may co-sponsor these Promotions with third party organizations, and may be required to share demographic information for the purposes of administering the applicable Promotion. Any shared demographic information will not be associated with individual Users; it will only be presented as aggregated information.

In some cases, where you choose to enter a Promotion, that that Promotion’s sponsor may require us to share email information with them. A User's personal email information will not be released to any third party organization without the User's prior express consent and disclosure of the sponsor organization's name, and FuckPartner™ will request that such named sponsors uphold the privacy of the registrant's information by not distributing or sharing such information with any other businesses or organizations, and we will ensure that such sponsors agree to be bound by the terms of this Policy.

Should you not wish to receive notices or be considered for Promotions, please contact us using the information provided in Section 17 below. 

## 9) Disclosure and Retention of Personal Information.

By submitting your personal information on the Website, you agree that we may share such personal information in order to complete your request for FuckPartner™ products and/or services, and that they may use such personal information for any lawful purposes, subject to any restrictions contained herein.

We may sell, rent, lease or otherwise provide the personal information that you supply to us (other than sensitive information such as credit card number), to any third party and we may work with other businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our users. These businesses and third parties may include, but are not limited to: (a) providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation; (b) e-mail marketers; (c) telemarketers (where permitted by applicable law); (d) SMS text-based marketers (where permitted by applicable law); and (e) direct marketers.

We may also employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include sending direct and electronic mail, removing duplicate information from user lists, analyzing data and providing marketing analysis. The agents performing these limited functions on our behalf shall have access to our users’ personal information as needed to perform their functions for us but we do not permit them to use your personal information for other purposes.

We will also use your personal information for customer service, to provide you with information that you may request, to customize your experience on the Website and/or to contact you when necessary in connection with transactions entered into by you on the Website. We may also use your personal information for internal business purposes, such as analyzing and managing our business. We may also combine the information we have gathered about you with information from other sources. We may use third parties to help us operate our business and the Website or to administer activities on our behalf.

By registering at the Website, you agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR §310 et seq.), as amended from time to time (the “Rule”) and applicable state do-not-call regulations. As such, notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call List, and/or on applicable state do-not-call lists, we retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the Rule and applicable state do-not-call regulations.

In addition, by submitting your personal information at the Website, you agree to receive mobile marketing including, but not limited to, text-message based marketing, from us and our third party advertisers and marketers (where, and to the extent that, such marketing is permitted by applicable law). As such, notwithstanding that your mobile telephone number may be listed on state and/or federal Do-Not-Call registries, we retain the right to contact you via text-message based marketing in accordance with applicable state and federal law. Further, you agree that we reserve the right to share, sell, rent, lease and/or otherwise distribute your mobile telephone and other mobile data with/to any third-party for any and all non-marketing uses permitted by this Privacy Policy and applicable law. The following are additional instances where we may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  1. Where this information must be shared to provide a product or service that you have requested.
  2. Where we need to send the information to companies that work on our behalf to provide a product or service to you.
  3. To investigate and/or enforce violations of our Terms and Conditions and/or this Policy, or to protect our interests and/or our legal rights and protections.
  4. To investigate potentially fraudulent or questionable activities.
  5. When required or permitted by law. FuckPartner™ (including our affiliates, advertisers and content providers) independently reserves the right to fully cooperate with requests from any recognized law enforcement authority, and to court orders, requesting or directing FuckPartner™ (including our affiliates, advertisers and content providers) to disclose the identity or other information regarding any person who is using or has used the Website or Service or has obtained any content available through or in association with the Website and/or Service. By accepting this Policy and using the Website and/or Service, you waive and hold harmless FuckPartner™, our affiliates, content providers, advertisers and the operators of the Website from any and all claims resulting from any and all actions taken by any of the foregoing during, or as a result of any law enforcement authority's investigations or inquiries.
  6. In the course of a sale or potential sale, reorganization, consolidation, merger or amalgamation of FuckPartner™. In order to ensure a smooth transition of the Service in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of all or substantially all of its assets or the sale of an individual website owned by FuckPartner™, FuckPartner™ may transfer your personally identifiable information to a third party as a part of such merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale. In the event the transaction proceeds, we will require that the receiving party agree that they will be similarly bound by the provisions of this Policy and that they will only use and disclose your personal information as we are similarly entitled under this Policy. In the event the sale does not proceed, we will require that the potential purchaser not use or disclose your personal information in any manner whatsoever and to completely erase same.
  7. Where such disclosure is described elsewhere in this Policy. This Policy does not protect information you post to any online profile, bulletin board, e-note, video chat room or any other forum accessible to other Users or other websites available via FuckPartner™.

## 10) Location of Personal Information.

We are an international organization with servers located in various jurisdictions. As a result, User personal information may be transferred to and stored in Canada, Ireland or elsewhere. We do the best we can to ensure your personal information is protected to the greatest extent possible. Where our registration/application process prompts Users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card information), and when we store and transmit such sensitive information, that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. However, please note that the jurisdiction in which we store your personal information may not have similar standards for protecting your personal information as are provided for in your country. In addition, government organizations from the jurisdiction in which the personal information is stored may have access to your personal information in accordance with the laws of such jurisdiction. 

## 11) Employee Access to Your Personal Information.

In the course of daily operations, access to private, sensitive and confidential information is restricted to authorized employees who have a legitimate business purpose and reason for accessing it. As a condition of their employment, all employees of FuckPartner™ are required to follow this Policy and our other written guidelines. Employees are informed about the importance of privacy and they are required to agree to a code of conduct that prohibits the disclosure of any personal information to unauthorized individuals or parties.

Unauthorized access to and/or disclosure of personal information by an employee of FuckPartner™ is strictly prohibited. All employees are expected to maintain the confidentiality of personal information at all times and failing to do so will result in appropriate disciplinary measures, which may include dismissal. 

## 12) Our Commitment to Data Security.

The security of your personal information is a priority to FuckPartner™.

User accounts are secured by member-created passwords. We use reasonable measures to protect registration and membership information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to User information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff, and such employees shall be required to respect the privacy of that information.

In the event that personal information is transferred to a third party, FuckPartner™ will take steps to ensure that such recipients safeguard the personal information and use the information only for authorized purposes. Some examples of such measures are as follows: 

  1. Physical security measures such as restricted access facilities and locked filing cabinets.
  2. Electronic security measures for computerized personal information such as password protection, database encryption and personal identification numbers.
  3. Organizational processes such as limiting access to such personal information to a selected group of individuals.
  4. Contractual obligations with third parties who need access to personal information by agreements stipulating the confidentiality of the information and requiring them to protect and secure the personal information.

In addition, where our registration/application process prompts Users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card information), and when we store and transmit such sensitive information, that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. 

## 13) Our Commitment to Children's Privacy.

Protecting the privacy of the very young is important to us. For that reason, we do not knowingly collect or maintain information from individuals under eighteen (18) years of age, and no part of FuckPartner™ is structured to attract anyone under eighteen (18) years of age. If you are younger than eighteen (18) years of age, you are not permitted to use the Website. FuckPartner™ encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children. 

## 14) Websites Governed by this Privacy Policy.

Only the [www.fuckpartner.com](http://www.fuckpartner.com/) website is governed by this Policy. The Website may contain links to other third party websites that are not governed by this Policy. Although we endeavor to only link to websites with high privacy standards, our Policy will no longer apply once you leave the Website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by other third party websites, nor are we responsible for the content of any such web property, company or organization that we do not control. Further, we cannot control and are not responsible for the actions of the employees, agents or assigns of any such web property, company or organization. Therefore, we suggest that you examine the privacy policies of those websites to learn how your information may be collected, used, shared and disclosed. 

## 15) Terms and Conditions, Notices and Revisions.

Your use of the Website, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Policy as well as our Terms and Conditions and all of its dispute resolution provisions including, but not limited to, limitations of liability and governing law. 

## 16) Updating this Privacy Policy.

This Policy is subject to change by FuckPartner™ at any time. We may modify any of the terms contained in this Policy at any time in our sole discretion; provided, however, that any amendment or modification to the arbitration provisions, prohibition on class actions provisions or any other provisions applicable to dispute resolution (collectively, “Dispute Resolution Provisions”) shall not apply to any disputes arising prior to the applicable amendment or modification. Any changes to our Privacy Policy and information handling practices will be acknowledged in this Policy in a timely manner. Subject to the above restrictions, we may add, modify or remove portions of this Policy when we feel it is appropriate to do so. You may determine when this Policy was last updated by referring to the date at the top of this Policy.

If any modification to this Policy is unacceptable to you, you agree that your only recourse is to terminate this Policy. Your continued use of the Service following our posting of a change notice or new agreement on the Website will constitute your binding acceptance of the change (other than with respect to disputes arising prior to the amendment or modification of the Dispute Resolution Provisions, which shall be governed by the Dispute Resolution Provisions then in effect at the time of the subject dispute).

BY PROVIDING PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US YOU SIGNIFY YOUR CONSENT TO OUR COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS POLICY. 

## 17) Opting Out, Contact Us, Questions and Suggestions.

During registration, application, purchase and/or when you otherwise submit personal information to us at the Website, you have opted-in and authorized us to share your personal information with third-parties for marketing purposes. To stop receiving future communications from FuckPartner™, please Click Here. To opt-out of having your information shared with third-parties, please Click Here. FuckPartner™ uses personal information to provide promotional offers by e-mail to individuals. FuckPartner™ and/or its marketing partners may maintain separate e-mail lists for different purposes. If e-mail recipients wish to end their e-mail subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each e-mail message to unsubscribe from that particular list.

If you have any further questions or concerns about this Policy, FuckPartner's™ privacy policies and use of personal information, please contact us using our online contact form, or by email at help@fuckpartner.com. 

## 18) Dispute Resolution.

Any claim or cause of action you may have arising from, connected with, or relating to this Policy or FuckPartner's™ handling of your personal information, or any related matters will be subject to the Dispute Resolution Provisions set forth in the Terms and Conditions and must be commenced within six (6) months after the claim or cause of action arises, after which time the claim or cause of action is forever barred, regardless of any statute or law to the contrary.
